Working for almost three years as a Web Content Manager in Vienna gave me my first practical experience in managing multiple websites as well as coordinating content and graphic releases with the marketing team.

As an **Integrations Web Designer** I aided in the construction of new web tools and made improvements to existing ones, using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

I recently finished the SheCodes Plus online training path which helped me to further build on my knowledge of Front End Development and Visualization.

Carina Huber

E-Mail:

hubercar.94@gmail.com

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/carina-huber

Skills

Technical

- Microsoft Office & G Suite
- Project management
- HTML5, CSS3, SASS
- Jira & Confluence
- CMS (Wordpress, Joomla)
- Git & Gitlab
- Visual Studio Code
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Bamboo Deployment
- SQL Databases
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript, React.js

Personal

- Quick comprehension
- Conflict Resolution
- Passionate
- Organized
- Thoughtful

Languages

English - Fluent German - Native Language

Experience

Manchester

07/2020 to present

Customer Advisor – Booking.com

- Customer support in German and English via Phone, Mail & Livechat
- Time Management, Task organisation, System Tracking

(Secondment) 01/2019 to 06/2020

Integrations Web Designer – Booking.com

- Colour Scheme Design for Partner White Labels for example Jet2carhire, TopCashback or Wizz Air
- Customization and deployment for Affiliate web products
- Facilitate regression tests and optimize usability
- Static banner creation

06/2018 to 12/2018

Customer Relations Advisor - Rentalcars.com

Advising Customers and helping to investigate on incident cases

Vienna 08/2015 to 02/2018

Web Content Manager – Reed Exhibitions

- Web content management on responsive sites for B2C & B2B events
 For example Vienna Comic Con or Tracht&Country
- Online Ticket shop adoption and support

Education

09/2010-06/2015

A-Levels/similar in Media Information Technology

HLW 10 Vienna – with focus at Web Programming and Software Design

03/2018 to 05/2018

Graphic Design Course

Extension of Skills in Adobe Photoshop, InDesign & Illustrator

Reference

Paul Gwyther – Lead Integrations Engineer at Booking.com paul.gwyther@booking.com